{
  "uniqueId": 1,
  "name": "Hiragana Reading Quiz",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below character in Romaji!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "NONE",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "NONE",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_QUESTION",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "cards": [
    {"question":"あ","answer":["a"]},
    {"question":"い","answer":["i"]},
    {"question":"う","answer":["u"]},
    {"question":"え","answer":["e"]},
    {"question":"お","answer":["o"]},
    {"question":"か","answer":["ka"]},
    {"question":"き","answer":["ki"]},
    {"question":"く","answer":["ku"]},
    {"question":"け","answer":["ke"]},
    {"question":"こ","answer":["ko"]},
    {"question":"が","answer":["ga"]},
    {"question":"ぎ","answer":["gi"]},
    {"question":"ぐ","answer":["gu"]},
    {"question":"げ","answer":["ge"]},
    {"question":"ご","answer":["go"]},
    {"question":"さ","answer":["sa"]},
    {"question":"し","answer":["shi"]},
    {"question":"す","answer":["su"]},
    {"question":"せ","answer":["se"]},
    {"question":"そ","answer":["so"]},
    {"question":"ざ","answer":["za"]},
    {"question":"じ","answer":["ji"]},
    {"question":"ず","answer":["zu"]},
    {"question":"ぜ","answer":["ze"]},
    {"question":"ぞ","answer":["zo"]},
    {"question":"た","answer":["ta"]},
    {"question":"ち","answer":["chi"]},
    {"question":"つ","answer":["tsu"]},
    {"question":"て","answer":["te"]},
    {"question":"と","answer":["to"]},
    {"question":"だ","answer":["da"]},
    {"question":"ぢ","answer":["di", "dzi"]},
    {"question":"づ","answer":["du", "dzu"]},
    {"question":"で","answer":["de"]},
    {"question":"ど","answer":["do"]},
    {"question":"な","answer":["na"]},
    {"question":"に","answer":["ni"]},
    {"question":"ぬ","answer":["nu"]},
    {"question":"ね","answer":["ne"]},
    {"question":"の","answer":["no"]},
    {"question":"は","answer":["ha", "wa"]},
    {"question":"ひ","answer":["hi"]},
    {"question":"ふ","answer":["fu", "hu"]},
    {"question":"へ","answer":["he", "e"]},
    {"question":"ほ","answer":["ho"]},
    {"question":"ば","answer":["ba"]},
    {"question":"び","answer":["bi"]},
    {"question":"ぶ","answer":["bu"]},
    {"question":"べ","answer":["be"]},
    {"question":"ぼ","answer":["bo"]},
    {"question":"ぱ","answer":["pa"]},
    {"question":"ぴ","answer":["pi"]},
    {"question":"ぷ","answer":["pu"]},
    {"question":"ぺ","answer":["pe"]},
    {"question":"ぽ","answer":["po"]},
    {"question":"ま","answer":["ma"]},
    {"question":"み","answer":["mi"]},
    {"question":"む","answer":["mu"]},
    {"question":"め","answer":["me"]},
    {"question":"も","answer":["mo"]},
    {"question":"や","answer":["ya"]},
    {"question":"ゆ","answer":["yu"]},
    {"question":"よ","answer":["yo"]},
    {"question":"ら","answer":["ra"]},
    {"question":"り","answer":["ri"]},
    {"question":"る","answer":["ru"]},
    {"question":"れ","answer":["re"]},
    {"question":"ろ","answer":["ro"]},
    {"question":"わ","answer":["wa"]},
    {"question":"を","answer":["wo", "o"]},
    {"question":"きゃ","answer":["kya"]},
    {"question":"きゅ","answer":["kyu"]},
    {"question":"きょ","answer":["kyo"]},
    {"question":"しゃ","answer":["sha"]},
    {"question":"しゅ","answer":["shu"]},
    {"question":"しょ","answer":["sho"]},
    {"question":"ちゃ","answer":["cha"]},
    {"question":"ちゅ","answer":["chu"]},
    {"question":"ちょ","answer":["cho"]},
    {"question":"にゃ","answer":["nya"]},
    {"question":"にゅ","answer":["nyu"]},
    {"question":"にょ","answer":["nyo"]},
    {"question":"ひゃ","answer":["hya"]},
    {"question":"ひゅ","answer":["hyu"]},
    {"question":"ひょ","answer":["hyo"]},
    {"question":"りゃ","answer":["rya"]},
    {"question":"りゅ","answer":["ryu"]},
    {"question":"りょ","answer":["ryo"]},
    {"question":"ん","answer":["n"]}
]}
  